Guide to the Duke Family Papers, 1885-1992 (bulk 1892-1927)
Duke University. University Archives
- Divorce Proceedings, James B. Duke v. Lillian Duke, 1892-1907
  - Deposition, Herbert W. Knight On Petition for Divorce, J.B. Duke v. Lillian Duke. 1906 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda of Authorities concerning Writ of Error to the Supreme Court of the U.S., J.B. Duke v. Lillian Duke. 1906 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Opinion, “On petition for divorce on the ground of adultery, charged with Huntoon, who appeared under the statue and was made a defendant. Final hearing on bill, answer and proof.” 1906 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Decree of Affirmance between J.B. Duke, Lillian Duke, and Frank T. Huntoon from the N.J. Court of Errors and Appeals. June 17, 1907 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Preparatory material and summary of related legal suits that were tried under the Act of 1902, Chapter 157. This was the statute that Duke v. Duke was brought against. 1905 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Accounts and logs of Mr. and Mrs. Duke’s whereabouts (according to detectives?). June 1905–July 1905, November 1905–January 1906 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Reports of operatives hired to record the daily activities of Mrs. L. Duke. October 1905–December 1905, May 1906 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Reports of operatives hired to record the daily activities of Mrs. L. Duke. January 1906–March 1906 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Reports of operatives hired to record the daily activities of Mrs. L. Duke. April 1906 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Summary, J.B. Duke v. Lillian Duke, Court of Error and Appeals. Vol. II. 1906 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Publication, New York Inquirer, “Notes on Society and Other Matters” (January 19, 1906), and other newspaper articles. 1905–1906 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - James B. Duke copy of The American Tobacco Company Agreement and By-Laws, 1908 Mar (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Architectural Records, Circa 1920s, 1935
  The architectural records include one drawing for J.B. Duke's home in Charlotte, North Carolina. The remaining architectural records document the residence of Walker P. Inman in Georgetown County, South Carolina.
  - Partial First Floor Plan, Residence for James B. Duke, Charlotte, NC. Charles C. Hook, architect. [1920s]. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM1)
  - Residence of Walker P. Inman, Esq., Georgetown County, S.C., Plot Plan, Sheet 1. Wyeth & King, architects. 1935 Jun 1. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM2)
  - Residence of Walker P. Inman, Esq., Georgetown County, S.C., Cellar Plan, Sheet 2. Wyeth & King, architects. 1935 Jun 1. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM2)
  - Residence of Walker P. Inman, Esq., Georgetown County, S.C., First Floor Plan, Sheet 3. Wyeth & King, architects. 1935 Jun 1. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM2)
  - Residence of Walker P. Inman, Esq., Georgetown County, S.C., Second Floor Plan, Sheet 4A. Wyeth & King, architects. 1935 Jun 1. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM2)
  - Residence of Walker P. Inman, Esq., Georgetown County, S.C., North Elevation, Sheet 5. Wyeth & King, architects. 1935 Jun 1. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM2)
  - Residence of Walker P. Inman, Esq., Georgetown County, S.C., South or River Elevation, Sheet 6. Wyeth & King, architects. 1935 Jun 1. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM2)
  - Residence of Walker P. Inman, Esq., Georgetown County, S.C., East Elevation, West Elevation, Sheet 7. Wyeth & King, architects. 1935 Jun 1. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM2)
  - Residence of Walker P. Inman, Esq., Georgetown County, S.C., Section Looking through West Wing, Sheet 8. Wyeth & King, architects. 1935 Jun 1. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM2)
  - Residence of Walker P. Inman, Esq., Georgetown County, S.C., Plans, Sheet 9A. Wyeth & King, architects. 1935 Jun 1. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM2)
  - Residence of Walker P. Inman, Esq., Georgetown County, S.C., Elevations and Sections, Sheet 10A. Wyeth & King, architects. 1935 Jun 1. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM2)
  - Residence of Walker P. Inman, Esq., Georgetown County, S.C., Plans-Elevations & Section, Sheet 11. Wyeth & King, architects. 1935 Jun 1. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM2)
  - Residence of Walker P. Inman, Esq., Georgetown County, S.C., Section through Guest Room No.1 Looking East, Section through Dining Room Looking West Towards Kitchen, Sheet No. 500. Wyeth & King, architects. 1935 Jun 1. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM3)
  - Residence of Walker P. Inman, Esq., Georgetown County, S.C., Living Room, Sheet No. 501. Wyeth & King, architects. 1935 Jun 1. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM3)
  - Residence of Walker P. Inman, Esq., Georgetown County, S.C., Gun Room & Dining Room, Sheet No. 502. Wyeth & King, architects. 1935 Jun 1. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM3)
  - Residence of Walker P. Inman, Esq., Georgetown County, S.C., Gallery-Entrance & Stair Hall, Sheet No. 503. Wyeth & King, architects. 1935 Jun 1. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM3)
  - Residence of Walker P. Inman, Esq., Georgetown County, S.C., Typical Window Detail (also fixing cornice heights), Sheet No. 504. Wyeth & King, architects. 1935 Jun 1. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM3)
  - Residence of Walker P. Inman, Esq., Georgetown County, S.C., Electric Plans, Sheet No. 700. Wyeth & King, architects. 1935 Jun 1. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM3)
  - Residence of Walker P. Inman, Esq., Georgetown County, S.C., First Floor Electric Plan, Sheet No. 701. Wyeth & King, architects. 1935 Jun 1. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM3)
  - Residence of Walker P. Inman, Esq., Georgetown County, S.C., Garage Electric Plan, Sheet No. 702. Wyeth & King, architects. 1935 Jun 1. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM3)
  - Residence of Walker P. Inman, Esq., Georgetown County, S.C., F.S. Typical Window Detail, Sheet No. 1000. Wyeth & King, architects. 1935 Jun 1. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM3)
  - Residence of Walker P. Inman, Esq., Georgetown County, S.C., Cellar Plan, Drg. No. HP-1. Wyeth & King, architects. 1935 May 25. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM3)
  - Residence of Walker P. Inman, Esq., Georgetown County, S.C., First Floor Plan, Drg. No. HP-2. Wyeth & King, architects. 1935 May 25. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM3)
  - Residence of Walker P. Inman, Esq., Georgetown County, S.C., Second Floor Plan, Drg. No. HP-1. Wyeth & King, architects. 1935 May 25. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM3)
  - Residence of Walker P. Inman, Esq., Georgetown County, S.C., First Floor Plumbing & Heating, Drg. No. HP-4. Wyeth & King, architects. 1935 May 25. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM3)
  - Residence of Walker P. Inman, Esq., Georgetown County, S.C., Second Floor Plumbing & Heating, Drg. No. HP-5. Wyeth & King, architects. 1935 May 25. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder DKFM3)